Thank you for watching!
Here we go!
It's time for the “Halo! Stay, this time with Morning Musume。 90's Yamazaki Mate.
Wakana Matsumoto from Angelem.
This time, I'm going to introduce you to the two of them, so please bear with me until the end.
Please bear with me.
I was able to be the MC with Wakana, who is Yamazaki's favorite!
Yay, with Ms. Yamazaki!
I'm so happy!
Last time, it was Ayumi Ishida and Wakana.
Yamazaki and Wakana.
I thought it was great when they were doing it, and then it was my turn to do it.
I'm so happy.
When I saw that you and Yamazaki were on the schedule.
I immediately told my parents.
They said, “You're in it with Mr. Yamazaki.
I'm so happy. Thank you.
You know what I like about Wakana?
She's just so cute.
She's just the way I like her.
And I think she has a beautiful singing voice.
And when I'm with her, she's very solid.
Probably more solid than her eyes.
I feel safe when I'm with her.
Thank you very much.
I was also a fan of Ms. Yamazaki before I joined Angstrom. I used to go to Hello Show and Hello Project's official store and buy their goods.
Seriously? That's why it feels like a dream come true to be working with Ms. Yamazaki as an MC.
I'm looking forward to sharing the fun with you. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
As for our recent activities, we have started our autumn tour.
This tour is the last tour for Ayumi Ishida.
Morning Musume。24 will be held on December 6 at Yokohama Arena.
What kind of tour is it?
The title of the tour is “We can dance,” so it's going to be a fun tour with a lot of dancing.
I'm looking forward to it.
The tour is called “Angulum 10th anniversary tour 2024 autumn Roots” and it's going on now.
This tour is also Ms. Kawamura's last tour.
As the title says, this year marks the 10th anniversary of Angulum's foundation.
So, the setlist has an anniversary feel to it, and the costumes are sparkling and the production is something that has never been done before.
There will be many exciting performances that have never been seen before, so please come and join us.
And the final performance of Angelem will be held on Thursday, November 28th.
It will be held at the Nippon Budokan on Thursday, November 28th.
This will be the final live for Ms. Kamura, and I hope to show you the culmination of all of our efforts as residents.
Please take a look at the video below.
Yuyukankan Gabouri Live
Tekuto means bubbles, and good things are good.
What if you're tired of being “kanpekusik”?
Yuukan Gabourieh Live
When lies are exposed, conscience carves up the enemy
a cluster of world numbers prickles in my chest
I don't want the tears to flow, but
Always
You're really doing your best
You've got to believe in yourself, too
The end will come, don't worry, don't worry, don't worry
You just have to take it one step at a time.
No more hiding. Forget about it.
I'm going to take a bath
Everything is gonna be alright
Tomorrow is gonna be alright
The future is gonna be alright
You don't love me, you're just a socialite
I know, I know, I know. That's what I'm talking about.
I know what you mean. I know what you mean.
I'm not so much an organa as an easy thing to say.
You You Come Come Gonna be alright
You haven't even been born 100,000 days yet
So I'm aware of it, and I'm always on edge because of my sins
When I feel like giving up, I do it lightly
I won't lie to myself
My heart beats in my chest, it's the truth
I can handle it. With you, it's aye aye aye
Someday, Kimi.
We'll be happy together
Whatever. If you're hungry.
Let's go eat yakiniku cold
Everything is gonna be alright
You You Come Come Gonna be alright
Other numbers sometimes prickle and ache in my chest
Paint it and let it flow I'm out
You're always trying so hard, you're always trying so hard
You believe in yourself, too, don't you?
I want more excitement
I want a solid block.
Theories are always fuzzy.
But if you can get your resolution up and your eye game moving...
You'll find more and more things you can't get right.
We'll figure it out. We'll figure it out. Don't worry, don't worry, don't worry.
We'll just have to take it one step at a time.
I don't care what you do, just get it all done.
Oh No No It's gonna work
Everything is gonna be alright
Oh, yeah
Tomorrow is gonna be alright
No No No No
The future is gonna be alright
Oh Yeah
No No No No No
Every day is gonna be alright
Oh Yeah
Everything is gonna be alright
Let's do our best together
Yamazaki Mate from Morning Musume。 24
Wakana Matsumoto of Angelem presents “Halo! stay” from Morning Musume 24.
From here, I would like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly and attentively.
I'll give you a quick answer.
Wakana Matsumoto is a good cook!
Which autumn delicacy would you like to cook?
Chestnuts
Chestnuts.
In about two months, Angulum will celebrate its 10th anniversary. When do you feel the history of the group?
When performing a song from a release event I've been to.
Where would you like to go out together next?
I want to go to a theme park with Ms. Yamazaki.
What do you like about Mei Yamazaki?
The moment I meet Ms. Yamazaki, she has a sparkling smile and rushes to me saying “Wakana-chan”.
What would you like to do with Ms. Kawamura in the remaining time until her graduation?
Visiting cafes.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
First of all, what do you like about Mei?
I can tell the moment I see her, right? The moment our eyes meet, she has a big smile on her face and rushes to me.
I'm so happy to see him run up to me like this, and I always get a lot of panda power from him.
I'm so happy to see him, and the last thing I want to do with Mr. Carbler is to go on a cafe tour.
I've been going out with Mr. Carburetor for a while now, going to cafes and coffee shops.
Mr. Curbler, I also like to eat and I like cute things, so it would be nice if we could go out together to eat some cute sweets.
Please post your questions to Mr. Yamazaki after the vtr.
Halostei
I'm sure it will be decided when I cry painful tears...
You're always really trying your best.
Believe in yourself too.
Oh, it's going to be okay, don't worry, don't worry, don't worry, don't worry
Angulum New Single Yuyukankan Ganaviolite
November 13 On Sail
Haloste
Next, I would like to ask Mr. Yamazaki a question from me.
I'll do my best.
Speaking of Mr. Yamazaki, he is Mr. Panda.
What was the moment when you felt the power of Mr. Panda the most recently?
The video of Panda san I saw before the festival.
You released your second photo book on the 14th of last month.
What would you do if you released a photo book?
What scenes did you try when you were shooting?
I tried on some boyish clothes.
Ms. Yamazaki's blog posts are always full of text.
What is your main point when writing?
I write down what's happening at the time.
If I were to cook for you, what would you like to eat?
I'd like to make a house of sweets together!
Sounds fun!
With only a few days left until Ayumi Ishida's graduation, please tell us about her influence on you. She was very good at teaching dance and made it very easy to understand.
Thank you very much. I'd like to ask you about something that caught my attention.
What kind of clothes did you wear for the photo shoot, where you were dressed like a boy?
It was very detective-like.
I wanted to make it look like a boy, so I tied my hair back and put it in a hat.
Not with a wig or anything, but in a bun.
Yes, put it all together.
I like it.
Take a look.
I'm really interested in it.
And if I'm cooking, I'd like to make a house of sweets with you.
Do you have any particular sweets that you would like me to use?
I like chocolate, so I'd like you to use chocolate.
Or marshmallows.
I want you to make a panda.
I want you to put it inside a panda.
A panda that can eat a panda?
Yes.
A panda that you can eat and put inside your house.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It sounds a little difficult, but I'm interested in it.
Let's make it.
Hallo! We'll continue after this.
Next time notice
I'm Ruwa Hattori, an 11-year-old 6th grader from Aichi Prefecture.
I have loved watching female idol groups on TV since I was little.
Among them, I especially liked Airi Suzuki of Cute, which made me interested in Halo Pro.
I was not old enough to audition at that time.
I waited until I was old enough to audition and auditioned.
I really enjoy singing and dancing to various songs at the trainee presentations.
I like various songs such as Hatsukoi Cider, Mousou Dake wa Freedom, Otona no Jijo, Tama no Iro, Oki Hitomi, etc.
I especially admire Airi Suzuki.
She is a cheerful girl who smiles a lot, but is also said to be a crybaby.
I'm afraid I'm not a crybaby.
Thank you very much.
My favorite food is stewed hamburger steak made by my mom and pumpkin curry made by my dad.
My favorite sport is basketball.
My favorite animal is a koala. My favorite subjects are social studies and music.
In music, I like to sing in class. My homeroom teacher is a social studies teacher.
She used to teach me a lot about social studies.
I like social studies very much because my homeroom teacher is a social studies teacher and she taught it to me very well.
My favorite colors are lavender, mint green and mustard.
I'm not very good at baking yet, but I'm a baker.
I once made melon bread. It was totally different from the melon bread they sell.
But it turned out delicious!
I would like to visit Shanghai because Tsubaki Factory had a live concert in Shanghai.
My charm point is the hair on my forehead.
My special skill is sign language.
When I went to a festival, there was a place that held a sign language class.
That's when I got interested in sign language and started signing.
I greet everyone in sign language!
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you for your continued support!
I'm ready for the end of this love journey, whatever the end may be.
I get so nervous when I'm on stage by myself.
I felt like I was on the edge of my seat.
I felt like I didn't have enough energy.
I want to get more physical so that I won't be nervous.
When I sing and dance a lot together, I get out of breath.
I want to be able to avoid shortness of breath.
Thank you for watching!
From now on, I will do my best to be a wonderful idol who can sing and dance at the same time.
I'll do my best to be a wonderful idol who can sing and dance at the same time.
Kismi, don't let go.
Kismi, keep it natural.
Wipe away this anxiety.
Touch me with your fingertips
Touch me with your eyes
Wrap me in your arms
Please Please
I love you
This time we have Rua Hattori as a Halo Pro trainee. Wakana, do you have any connection with Rua?
I don't have any direct contact with Rua-chan, but when I was a trainee accompanying her at the summer HaloCon, I saw Rua-chan Hattori offstage.
When Rua Hattori was with the trainees at the summer HaloCon, I saw Rua Hattori watching the monitor offstage all the time, and when she went to the cheering section, she memorized the choreography in advance and danced with the members.
I saw Rua Hattori dancing with the members after memorizing the choreography in advance when she went to the cheering section.
You know, she's amazing, isn't she?
I'd like to talk to you again sometime.
I was a guest performer at the low-pro trainee recital, and we sang a song called “Rebellion” together.
But she was so tiny!
She was so tiny, but she was moving around, and the sound effects were so cute.
Yamazaki-san, you were a trainee at the time, was there anything memorable?
I was a trainee in Hokkaido.
I was working in Hokkaido.
I was working in Hokkaido, but I went to Tokyo for the diagnostic test.
I was working with other trainees in Tokyo.
If I won an award there
I was supposed to be able to participate in the Halo Pro trainee presentation in June.
I worked hard to get the award.
I worked really hard to get the award, and then I was going to be in the show.
That's amazing.
How old were you then?
I was about 11 years old when I entered.
I think I entered when I was about 11 years old, in the fifth grade.
That's amazing.
Since you were 11 years old?
That's right. So I think you and Rua are about the same age.
That's right.
Tea oma.
I am Natsuyaki Kimiyabi.
I am Natsume Nakayama of Ocha no Oma.
I will continue to have fun and do my best.
Now, what will you make this time? Today, we are going to make Soumen tea.
Well, I started to cook a lot after my last performance, and I am looking forward to cooking again this time.
I will do my best. I look forward to working with you.
Shredded, shredded all over?
It's fluffy. It's fluffy.
I've never had eggs like this before.
Now then, let's boil the noodles first.
Here it is already out of the blue.
Miyamizu Point
Boil the noodles shortly.
That's right, so I'll fry them.
That's right.
Does that mean it's quite short?
It says 1.5 to 2 minutes.
Half a minute.
One minute.
Sure, it's almost there, isn't it?
That's right.
Here we go.
One minute. Oh, start.
Thank you very much.
Mitsume, there's something you're still into.
That's right.
So many things.
It's all in the direction of stories, really.
That's exactly what I've been doing since I started cooking.
At first, I honestly thought it was enough to eat.
But as I started cooking, I started to care more and more about the presentation and the way it looks.
I'm getting more and more interested in the presentation and how it looks.
Recently, I've become addicted to collecting china
I'm into collecting plates.
It's nice.
You're a girl who really likes to cook.
I'm starting to love it.
Like, “Let's use this plate for this dish.
Yes, yes.
Until now, the plates we had at home were really just the bare essentials, so I thought I'd find something a little fancy.
So when she finds something stylish...
I'm going to buy them.
Here they are!
I'll do it, sir.
Oh, it's dangerous.
It's a little dangerous.
I see. Well, that's good, but...
But it's a little out of the ordinary.
Oh!
Wash it well, then.
Like this, it's very slimy, so it's a little bit like flour.
Wash it well.
It feels hard to the touch, doesn't it?
It's still a little...
There's a core, like this.
After the water has drained off.
Pour sesame oil over the noodles and let it soak in.
It's about one round, right?
A little bit by hand.
And again.
Shall I pour it on?
It smells so good.
The oil is good.
It looks delicious.
I think I can eat it now.
Let's continue.
Now it's time to start grilling!
Let's grill the fried tofu and spam.
When they turn brown, take them out.
Then vegetables.
Yes, sir.
It's okay if there's a little or a lot.
Or all of them.
I heard you went to Okinawa with a group recently.
How was that?
We did a 47 prefecture tour in Okinawa.
We did some light filming the next day.
Everyone was pretty casual about it.
We thought it was our day off, so we had a lot of fun.
10 of us.
This was the first time this year that we all went out somewhere and had fun.
We had a barbecue.
We had a barbecue, we split up into groups, and I tried snorkeling.
I felt like I was having a good time with my youth.
You're having fun this summer, aren't you?
I'm having a great time.
Like barbecuing?
And this is the first time you've had a barbecue with all the members?
It's the first time.
Sounds like fun.
Of course it was fun, and it was delicious.
But I don't know what's the difference between the members who barbecue, the members who eat, and the members who skip the barbecue.
The members who skip it.
It shows your personality, doesn't it?
By the way, who is the member who skips out?
Kina Yonemura.
That was Kina Yonemura.
We had some yakiniku, but they also prepared watermelon for us.
The fourth character loves watermelon.
She's eating watermelon.
You're eating it?
It's not cut, it's not cut.
He's eating it cut up.
You know, like, when you're cooking or something.
Or when you're having a sleepover, of course.
I'm sure you're staying over, so... you know, whatever happened there.
Anything you haven't...
Information that you haven't shared with anyone? Happenings?
Anything you haven't told us? Someone who never sleeps.
Or that there was a member who talked all night even though he said he was going to go to bed.
I think the funniest thing was in the morning.
That's why we were together from the time we went to bed until we woke up in the morning, right?
Like, “This girl talks a lot in her sleep.
I could tell that she was the type to wake up in the middle of the night.
When you spend this much time together, you gradually start to see things like that.
There are kids who talk in their sleep, too, you know.
I'm talking about Kira here, but she's the type that talks in her sleep.
Some people say things in their sleep.
She's saying “squishy squishy squishy.
It's coming along great, and it's getting closer to completion.
Almost done.
Maybe we can loosen the eggs a little.
I can already see Kansai.
It's taking shape.
If you turn up the heat too high, the noodles will stick together.
It's better to put the noodles where the ingredients are.
Okay.
That's fine.
Okay, thank you.
Ingredients are in.
I think I'm going to use chopsticks for this one.
Do I need to cut the noodles or anything?
No, I don't think so.
I heard a rumor that if you consult with Natsume, you'll get a great answer.
What's this?
Sensei, what's troubling you lately?
My daughter's not getting any taller.
I see.
How's that? Natsume.
This is difficult.
Nothing.
No questions.
There are no questions
Not accepted.
It's a lot more moist.
Let's see.
Bon appétit.
How do you like it?
It's done.
Is it done?
Thank you very much.
Looks good. How about like this?
I think it's good. It's done!
Oh, this way, this way, this way, this way...
Look out! Look out!
Safe! One more time!
Somen Chanpuru is ready!
How is it?
Better than I thought it would be!
I'm really looking forward to eating it now. Please enjoy it right away. Let's eat.
I'm the selector for this dish, so it's nice. Bon appétit.
You have arranged it beautifully.
Spam is delicious!
Then, I'll have the somen noodles, too.
Delicious!
You boiled it kind of fast, didn't you?
It's not hard at all!
Perfectly good! Delicious!
Amazing! You're right, just do it in half the time.
But I'll still let it cook a little later.
We're going to heat it up.
Cooking.
Well, I've started cooking since the last time I was at Hello Kitchen.
I think I've shown some growth, both to you and to the people who are watching.
I had an image of eating Soumen noodles only with Soumen noodles and Soumen sauce.
I was surprised to know that it can be arranged as a chanpuru like this.
I'd like to make it at home from now on.
I'd like to make some more difficult dishes that are a little more advanced.
So, thank you very much for your hard work this time.
Thank you very much. This is Hello Kitchen.
This is Hello Kitchen, a program of Morning Musume。 24's Yamatsuki Mate and Akeuna Matsumoto of Angulum. Stay Stay!
From here on, we'll be back with the Halo! Pro Pot Diary.
This time, I'd like to talk about our outing together, looking at the photos.
Now, I, Wakana Matsumoto, would like to introduce you to the photos I have chosen.
Here it is!
Did you get it?
I think this photo was taken more than a year ago, in August 2023.
This is probably the first day that Mr. Yamazaki and I went out together.
I found out about Panna's parfait.
I found out that Panna's parfait was available, and I thought I had to go there with Mr. Yamazaki to enjoy it.
I invited him to join us.
As you can see in the picture, it was a parfait with Panna's face on it.
As you can see in the picture, there is an ice cream or cookie with Panna's face on it.
It tasted delicious and looked so cute.
It was so much fun to spend time with Mr. Yamazaki!
The two shots of the parfait and Wakana were so cute!
Thank you very much!
We also took purikura (picture taking) that day.
We bought matching pins for Panna together.
It was a very fun day!
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Hallo! Sta!
Next, I, Mei Yamazaki, would like to introduce the photo I chose!
Here it is!
De-da-da!
This is a picture of me and Wakana at the Ueno Zoo.
Yes, we went there, didn't we?
Zo-panda!
Three shots!
They are so cute!
I wanted to see Zo Panda with Wakana.
We wanted to go see Zo Panda with Wakana, but it wasn't open that day, so we decided to go on a different day.
I was wearing a panda's catsuit, and I was wearing it with my elemens, and I was wearing it just before that.
I was wearing a panda pin when we went out for parfait the third time.
I wore a panda pin.
Her hair was like a panda's.
It was so cute.
Mr. Yamazaki gave me a panda patch for my clothes, too.
Mr. Yamazaki gave me a panda patch as a gift.
so I put a little bit of it on.
I also made my clothes with a panda in mind.
I'm so happy!
Just seeing the two shots of Ms. Panda and Wakana
I was so happy that day.
I'm glad
It was a day I'll never forget.
And you know, I saw a lot of animals besides pandas.
Wakana-chan
shows a red panda
I also got a shot of the red panda.
I love red pandas so much.
Whenever I go to the zoo
I often spend quite a long time looking at red pandas.
There is also a cute red panda in the zoo above this one.
He was moving around very energetically that day.
He was so cute!
I was so healed!
There were also gorillas and giraffes
There were a lot of gorillas and giraffes!
It was a really fun day because we saw so many things!
It was a lot of fun.
Please subscribe to our channel.
So that's it. Yes, Haloste.
We've been going places like this... but some people ask how we decide where to go.
I wonder how they decide... but the first time we did it...
I sent a message to Ms. Yamazaki at her birthday event saying that I wanted to go to eat her parfait at her birthday event, and she contacted me and we decided to go. So Mr. Yamazaki contacted me and we decided to go.
And the first time we went, we made a promise for the second time.
It's like we always have plans for the third time after the second time.
So we would send each other information about when we were free, and we would make reservations.
And Kana-chan is always there to show us the way.
When we went to eat ramen noodles, she told me it was this way.
I'm glad you came with me because it's a place I'd like to go too.
I'm glad you came with me.
I'm glad that you came with me because it's a place I'd like to visit.
My image of Ms. Yamazaki is that she speaks softly and has a relaxed atmosphere,
I had this image of you as a soft and fluffy person,
I had this fluffy image of Mr. Yamazaki, with his fluffy way of speaking and his relaxed atmosphere, but I also caught glimpses of him being surprisingly quick-witted and savvy,
I am very happy to have gotten to know various aspects of Mr. Yamazaki.
I am glad.
But at first, I mostly watched videos and performances,
I thought she was so small and danced so hard and big. I thought she was cute.
When I actually talked to her, I found out that she is very solid, more solid than I am, and she is a lot of fun to be with,
And if I say something weird, he just shoves it in my face.
If I say something weird, he just goes right into it. He goes into everything, so I think he's really interesting and fun to be with.
I can't stop talking to him after meeting him, and I always feel like it's time to say good-bye, so I hope we can hang out a lot more.
I hope we can hang out a lot again.
Thank you for watching.
Ruri will do her best, so let's do it together!
Morning Musume。24's Yamashiki Mate
Akeina Matsumoto of Angelem will be presenting “Halo! Sta.
It's time to say goodbye!
Wow, it's almost over!
It was so fast!
It went so fast.
It's like we have the same clothes.
I was so surprised.
White and new!
I was so happy to see them, it was like fate... fate... it was fun... here's an announcement!
Morning Musume。24 Concert Tour Autumn We Can Dance This weekend will be the Gunma Ibaraki concert.
And the final concert of the tour will be held on December 6 at Yokohama Arena, where Ayumi Ishida will be graduating.
We will do our best!
And Angulum's 10th anniversary tour 2024 autumn roots is now underway.
This weekend we will be performing in Kumamoto!
We will do our best in our hometown of Kuresa Kamiko!
The final concert of the tour will be held at Nippon Budokan on November 28th.
This is Kawamura-san's final live, so we will do our best to give you a sparkling live performance!
Morning Musume。24's new album “Professionals 17” will be released on November 27th.
Professionals 17 will be released on November 27th.
This album contains songs of various genres,
You will be able to see a lot of different aspects of us in one album,
Please listen to it!
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, Angelem will release a new single on November 13th. Hatsukoi Hanabi he, Yuyuukankankan ga Nanabiorai” are both A-side singles. Please listen to them a lot.
I'm going to go.
Project is a group of Hello! Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating, comment, and subscribe to our channel.
The other members were Yamazaki Mate from Morning Musume 24 and Matsumoto Akena from Angulum.
Goodbye!